Perls Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1937-1995, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-44, OV 81-83; 43.6 linear feet)
  - The House & Home Shop, 1963-1967 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Hubbard, Earl Wade, 1958-1959, 1985, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - The Hudson River Museum, 1976, 1983-1986 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Hunker, Robert L., 1960-1961 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Hunt Foods & Industries Museum of Art, 1967-1968, (see also Norton Simon Museum of Art; Norton Simon, Inc.; Simon, Norton) (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Huntington Galleries, 1964-1971 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Huppler, Dudley, 1946-1947 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Hyogo Preftural Museum of Modern Art, 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous H, circa 1937-1995, (25 folders) (Box 20, Folder 27-51)
  - IBM, 1966-1994 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Illinois Wesleyan University, 1947-1952 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Indiana University, 1972-1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Indiana University, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Indiana University, 1957-1969 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Indiana University, 1942-1948 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1970-1979, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The International Nickel Company, 1967-1973 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - The International Nickel Company, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston, 1955-1956, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art, Boston, 1938-1948 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Insurance Policies, 1948-1952 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Insurance Policies, 1938-1947 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Isaac Delgado Museum of Art, 1940, 1951-1961, 1970-1972, (see also New Orleans Museum of Art) (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Isenberg, Julie, 1951-1963 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - The Israel Museum, 1965-1968, 1974-1975, 1983, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous I, circa 1937-1995 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - J. Schwarzenbach & Co., 1961-1973 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - The J. B. Speed Art Museum, 1970-1984 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - The J. B. Speed Art Museum, 1962-1966 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - J. J. Klejman, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - The J. L. Hudson Gallery, 1965-1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Jack Lenor Larsen Inc., 1954-1955, 1962-1968 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Jackson, Charles, 1946-1956 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Jackson, Charles, 1944-1945 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Jacob, Erwin, 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Jacobi, Kurt E., 1940-1941 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Jacobson, Steven M., 1970-1975 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Jacques Seligmann & Co., 1939, 1946, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - James Bourlet & Sons, Ltd., 1956-1960 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - James, Oliver B., 1954 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Janie C. Lee Gallery, 1975-1990 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Jansson, Bert, 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Jaylen Offset Lithography Company, 1970-1978 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Jeffrey Loria & Co., Inc., 1968-1974, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Jenny, Alfred, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Jerald Melberg Gallery, 1986-1991 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Jewelers Protection Services Ltd., 1986-1990 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Jewelers Protection Services Ltd., 1978-1985 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - The Jewish Museum, 1967, 1984-1989 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - John and Mable Ringling Museum of Art, 1949, 1962-1965, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1945-1948 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - John Weiss Plumbing Corp., 1956-1967 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Johnson, Mrs. J. Lee (Ruth Carter), 1964-1976 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Johnson, Mrs. Lyndon B. (Lady Bird), 1967 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Johnston, H. Frederick, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Jonathan Cape Limited, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Jones, Thomas C. and Catherine, Jr., 1970-1974 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Jordan, Carroll, 1940-1943, 1949-1953 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Josefowitz, David, 1963-1970, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Josefowitz, Samuel, 1958-1979 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Joseph Safron Galleries, 1951-1952 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Joslyn Art Museum, 1948, 1957-1965, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Juan Alvarez del Vayo Fraud Matter, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Judah, Robin, 1977-1986, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Judah, Robin, 1966-1976 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Julius Lowy Frame & Restoring Company, Inc., 1965, 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Julius Lowy Frame & Restoring Company, Inc., 1953-1955 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Julius Lowy Frame & Restoring Company, Inc., 1949-1952 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - The Junior Art Gallery, 1951-1961 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Juviler, Adolphe A., 1952-1971 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Miscellaneous J, circa 1937-1995, (9 folders) (Box 22, Folder 1-9)
  - Kahn, Arthur E. and Anita, 1964-1982, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Kajikawa Trading Agency Co., Ltd., 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The Kalamazoo Institute of Arts, 1941-1944, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Kalliroscope Corporation, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Kameyama, Shigeki, 1977-1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Kane, Ruth D., 1943-1946 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - The Kansas City Art Institute, 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Kantor, Paul, 1955-1981 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Kaplan, Lewis M., 1969-1976 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Kardon, Robert, 1958-1974 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Karidis, Jerome, 1978-1982 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Karshan, David, 1973-1986 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - The Katonah Gallery, Inc., 1971-1975 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - The Katonah Gallery, Inc., 1957-1966 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Kaufman & Vinson Co., 1945-1953 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Keeler, Miner S. and Mary Anne, 1968-1976 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Keene State College, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Keitelman, Maurice, 1990-1994 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Kellen, Konrad, 1948, 1968, 1980, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Kende Galleries, Inc., 1948-1953 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Kenyon College, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Keosian, Jesse, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Ketterer, Roman Norbert, 1965-1979 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Ketterer, Roman Norbert, 1948-1949, 1957-1964 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Kiam, Victor, 1954-1961, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Kiko Gallery, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Killam, Walt, 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Kimbell Art Museum, 1974, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Kingsley, Johnston, 1941-1948 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Kinzinger, S. M. and Mary, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Kirkman, James, 1977-1983 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Klabal Gallery, 1977, 1983-1986 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Kleemann Galleries, 1938-1948 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Klein, Marvin E., 1969-1979 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Klinkhoff, Walter H., 1962, 1971-1973, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Knapp, Stefan, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Kniaseff, Mara, 1957-1970 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Koch, Edward I., 1968 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Kodansha, Ltd., 1975-1981, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Kolker, Berndt, 1938-1940, 1946, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - König, Irmgard, 1981-1987 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Krasner Gallery, 1966-1981 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Krieger, Frederick, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Krimmel, Bernd, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Krohg, Guy, 1982-1993 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Krohg, Lucy, 1953-1974 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Kruidenier, David, 1964-1968, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Kulicke Frames, Inc., 1956-1971 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Kunsthalle Bielefeld, 1983-1992 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Kunsthalle der Hypo-Kulturstiftung, 1987-1991 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Kunsthalle Köln, 1978-1983 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Kunsthandel Monet, 1967-1970 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Kunsthaus Lempertz, 1959-1968, 1983-1990 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Kunsthaus Zürich, 1953, 1964-1975, 1985-1991 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Kunstmuseum Luzern, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Kunstsammlung Nordrhein-Westfallen, 1990-1995 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Kunstsammlung Nordrhein-Westfallen, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Kunstsammlung Nordrhein-Westfallen, 1963-1976 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Kunstverlag Weingarten, 1989-1997 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Kurnitz, Harry, 1945, 1952-1954 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Miscellaneous K, circa 1937-1995, (19 folders) (Box 23, Folder 1-19)
  - Lacher, Frances, 1964-1970 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Lackritz, Harry, 1944-1946, 1952-1953 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Laemmle, Walter, 1940-1945 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - La More, Chet, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - La More, Chet, 1944-1945 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - La More, Mary, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Land, Edwin, 1947-1948, 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Landau Fine Art, 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Landsberger, Herbert H., 1958-1968 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Lane, Alvin S., 1969-1973, 1978-1981 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Lane, Alvin S., 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Lane, Alvin S., 1961-1965 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Lane, Jeffrey, 1985-1991 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Lang, Sylvan, 1955-1957, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Lardé, A., 1950-1962 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Lasker, Albert D. and Mary, 1942, 1950-1967 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Lasker, Louisa D., 1952-1961 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - La Tausca Art Competition, 1946-1947 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Latner, Albert J., 1968-1973, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Laurens, Frank, 1953-1962 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Laurent, Paul, 1974, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Lavin, Carl H., 1953, 1958, 1967, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Law, Theodore N. and Caroline W., 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Lawrence, Jack, 1945, 1952-1959, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Lawrence, Sidney, 1947-1948 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Layton Art Gallery, 1944-1948 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Lazarus, Charles Y., 1965, 1971-1973, 1981, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - League for Emotionally Disturbed Children, Inc., 1958 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Lebel, Robert, 1943-1956 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Le Blan, Philippe, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - LeClair, Charles, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Lee, Gypsy Rose, 1940-1943 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Lee, Herbert C. and Mildred, 1961-1966, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Leger, Richard, 1977-1987 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Leger, Richard, 1967-1976 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - LeGwin, J. D., Jr., 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Lehigh University, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - The Leicester Galleries, 1944-1950, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Lenore Gold Gallery, 1968-1973 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Leo Baeck Institute, 1972, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Leonardo Editore, 1989-1992 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Lep Transport, Inc., 1949-1951 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Levantal, Mrs. Leo (Françoise), 1949-1950, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Levee, Michael, 1968-1973 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Leventritt, M. Victor, 1953, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Levi, Robert H., 1967-1980 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Levin, Howard S. and Enid B., 1968-1973 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Levin, Isadore and Jeanne, 1937, 1954, 1961-1968 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Levinson, Charles B., 1975-1979 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Levy, Robert Chase, 1955-1956, 1962-1972 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Lewin, Albert, 1937-1939, 1945-1947 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, Barbara K., 1979-1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lewis, Elaine, 1978-1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Lewis, Eugene John, 1954, 1961-1962, 1967-1972, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Lewis, Mary, 1937-1942, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Lewis, Merrick, 1958-1970 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Lewis, Orme, 1967-1983 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Lexington Stationery Co., Inc., 1954-1966 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Lextown Window Cleaning Co., 1950-1955 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - The Library of Congress, 1946, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Liebholz, Franz, 1960-1972, 1975-1983 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Life Magazine, 1941-1948, 1956-1969 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Light, Robert M., 1958, 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Lilienfeld Galleries, 1937-1938, 1947-1954 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Linder, Bertram N., 1952-1965, 1975-1978 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Lineaweaver, John W., 1943-1953 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Lion, Fred, 1939-1943, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Lièe, Belgium, 1979-1984 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Lipman, Howard W. and Jean, 1969-1985, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Lipman, Howard W. and Jean, 1958-1968, (see also OV 81) (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Liss, Herman, 1956-1957 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - List, Albert A., 1961-1969 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - List, Albert A., 1946, 1953-1959 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Litvak, Anatole, 1947-1955 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Lloyd, Mrs. Horatio Gates, Jr., 1938-1939, 1945-1946, 1956, 1968-1982 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Loeb, Albert, 1965-1973, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Loeb, Mrs. Howard (Hortense), 1938-1943 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Loeb, John L., 1951-1969 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Loeb, Pierre, 1942-1943, 1950-1951 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Loeb, Pierre, 1939-1941 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Loew, David L., 1941-1944 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Logsdon, Kenneth Leslie, 1948-1953 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Lomax, Elizabeth, 1944-1945 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - London Arts Group, 1972-1982 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - London Arts Group, 1969-1971 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - London, Robert and Ellin, 1967-1972, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Long Beach Museum of Art, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Long Island University, 1968-1969, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Look Magazine, 1946-1969 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Lord's Gallery, 1955-1963 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1991-1995 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1988-1990 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1974-1987 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1968-1973 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1961-1967 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1939-1949, 1954, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Lott, John F., 1969-1973, 1984-1989 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Loudmer, Guy, 1971, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Louisiana Gallery, 1964-1969, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Louisiana Museum of Modern Art, 1968-1973, 1983-1990 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Lowe Art Museum, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Lowe, Frederick, 1951-1952 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Lowengard, Armand, 1939-1942 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Lowenthal, Milton and Edith, 1943-1954 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Lubitsch, Ernst, 1940,1945 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Luce, Mrs. Henry, III (Patricia), 1950-1951 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Luce, Henry R. and Clare Booth, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Ludwig, Peter, 1980-1983 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Lugene Inc., 1953-1971 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Lukas, Edwin J., 1941-1943 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Lust, Herbert and Virginia, 1964-1973 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Luther, Mrs. James H. (Catherine), 1950-1960 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Lutz, Walter G., 1947-1953 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous L, circa 1937-1995, (4 folders) (Box 24, Folder 64-67)
  - Miscellaneous L, circa 1937-1995, (24 folders) (Box 25, Folder 1-24)
  - M. Knoedler & Co., Inc., 1972-1990 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - M. Knoedler & Co., Inc., 1937-1969 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - M. H. de Young Memorial Museum, 1943-1944, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - M. M. Lane, 1954-1959 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - MacDonald, William A., 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - MacMillan Publishing Company, 19792-1975, 1980, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Mack, Norman E., II, 1961-1968, 1978-1979, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Macy's, 1946-1947 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Maeght, Adrien, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Maeght Editeur, 1984, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Maguy, Alex, 1985-1994 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Maguy, Alex, 1977-1984 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Maguy, Alex, 1971-1976 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Maguy, Alex, 1961-1970 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Maguy, Alex, 1955-1960 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Main Street Galleries, 1953, 1959-1963 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - The Mainichi Newspapers, 1979, 1990-1993 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - The Mainichi Newspapers, 1961-1968 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Makepeace, Le Roy, 1959, 1972, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Makler Gallery, 1982-1994 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Makler Gallery, 1978-1981 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Makler Gallery, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Makler Gallery, 1970-1974 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Makler Gallery, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Makler Gallery, 1966-1967 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Makler Gallery, 1964-1965 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Makler Gallery, 1957-1963 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Malek, Bernard J., 1959-1963 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Malitsky Art Books, 1955-1960, 1969-1971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Malkiel, Burton G., 1966-1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Mandelbaum, Robert and Helen, 1963-1980, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Manhattan Cable TV, Inc., 1968-1987 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Manhattan Floor Supplies, 1955-1976 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Manhattan Gallery, Tokyo, 1979, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Mansion House Center, 1969, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Marcus, Edward S., 1969-1972 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Marcus, Stanley, 1950-1955, 1971-1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Marcuse, James B., 1965-1974, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Marcuse, John, 1954-1961, 1969-1975 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Maremont, Arnold E., 1960-1964 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Maremont, Arnold E., 1953-1959 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Margaret Brown Gallery, 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Margulies, Martin Z., 1974, 1980-1981, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Marie Harriman Gallery, 1940-1941, 1949-1960 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Markson, Robert T., 1950-1953 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Markus, Henry A., 1958-1969 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Marlborough Gallery, 1947-1974, 1981, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Marshall Field & Company, 1949-1951 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Marshall, Jonathan, 1955-1972 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Marter, Joan M., 1972-1978 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Martha Jackson Gallery, 1955-1957, 1963-1973, 1979, (see also OV 81) (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Martin, Crozer F., 1951-1957 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Martin, Dean, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Martin House, 1966-1970 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Martin, Joe, 1944-1953 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Martinez-Pedro, Luis, 1947-1955 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Martinez-Pedro, Luis, 1944-1946 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Masereel, Frans, 1939-1947 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1968-1969, 1975-1977, 1985-1986, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Masteller, John R., 1945-1951, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Mathews, Irving, 1969-1972, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Mauric, Madeleine, 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Maxwell Davidson Gallery, 1973, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Maxwell Galleries, 1944, 1963-1967, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Maxwell, John R., 1946, 1974-1980, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - May, Morton D., 1949, 1955, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - May, Tom, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - May, Wilbur D., 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Mayer, Robert B., 1952-1954, 1963-1975 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - The Mayor Gallery, 1968-1991 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - McAshan, S. M., Jr., and Susan C., 1961-1962, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - McCormick, Mrs. Cyrus (Florence), 1956-1957 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - McCune, William J., Jr. and Elizabeth, 1966-1972 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - McDermott, Eugene and Margaret, 1965-1972 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - McGowan, Jack, 1944-1952 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - McGraw-Hill Publishing Company, 1971, 1977, 1990-1996 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - McKenna, Donald C., 1953-1966 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - McKennis, Philip C., 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - McLean, John R., 1945-1949 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - McNamara, Robert S., 1970 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - McNay Art Institute, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - McNay Art Institute, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - McNay Art Institute, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - McNay Art Institute, 1973-1979 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - McNay Art Institute, 1957-1958, 1964-1965 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Meadows, Algur H., 1967-1968 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Means, Glenn, 1947-1950, 1958, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - Medical Newsmagazine, 1957, 1966-1968, 1975-1980 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Mekler Gallery, 1980-1988 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Mellon, Paul, 1948-1952 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Meltzer, Robert, 1969-1979, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Menil Foundation, London, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Meredith, Burgess, 1957, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - Meridian Gallery, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Merlander, Kurt, 1946-1947 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - The Merrin Gallery, 1974-1995 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Messer, Charles H., 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Metcalf, Richard, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1980, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - Metzner, Sheila, 1986-1991 (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Meyer, Franz, 1962-1966, 1974-1980, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Michael, Charles, 1972-1977 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Michigan Bell Telephone Company, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Michigan State University, 1956-1959 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Midtown Galleries, 1962-1970, 1984-1988 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Mietschaninoff, Oscar, 1950-1956 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Il Milione, 1952-1955, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Arthur R., 1975-1981, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Miller, Donna, 1943-1948 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Miller, Edgar E., 1961-1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Millett, Stephen C., 1967-1968, 1976-1981 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Milton, A. Fenner, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Milton, Elizabeth Fenner, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Milwaukee Art Museum, 1965-1983 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Milwaukee Art Museum, 1942-1947, 1953-1959 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Minkoff & McMenamin (Corporate Taxes), 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - The Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1969-1980, 1990-1994 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - The Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1946-1948, 1955-1968 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Miró, Joan, 1957-1965 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Mitchell, Austin A., 1939-1951, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Mitsukoshi Museum of Art, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Mittman, Benjamin, 1968-1982 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - MIZUE, 1964-1968, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - MODARCO, S. A., 1970-1974 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Moderna Museet, 1973, 1982-1989 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Modern Art Foundry, 1961-1985 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Modern Master Tapestries Inc., 1971-1976 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Moeller, Achim, 1973-1975, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Monique de Groote Galerie d'Art, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Montague, Rosemary, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Montclair Art Association, 1944-1948, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Montgomery Gallery, 1984-1993 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, 1959-1964, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Moore, Henry, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Moran-Turner, 1966-1968 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Morot-Sir, Edouard, 1968, 1974, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Morrell, James F., 1968-1972, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Morris and Gwendolyn Cafritz Foundation, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Morris, Herbert C., 1960-1967 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Morris & McVeigh, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Morris & McVeigh, 1966-1974 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Morse, A. Reynolds, 1943-1950, 1957-1968, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Moser, Hugo, 1947-1954 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Motte, Marguerite, 1960-1980 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1950, 1978, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Mouradian, A. D., 1939, 1946-1947, 1953, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Moyse, Jacques, 1954-1978 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Muchow Associates, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Mudd, Henry T., 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Muller, Ernst F., 1941-1947, 1964-1971 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Mulnix, Mrs. LeVant (Nancy), 1970-1978 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Mulnix, Mrs. LeVant (Nancy), 1969 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Mulnix, Mrs. LeVant (Nancy), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1946-1948, 1954, 1960-1966, 1981, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Murphy, Keith R., 1953-1954 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Murray, Arthur T., 1938-1941 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Musée d'Art et d'Histoire, Geneva, 1970, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 56)